MOHAMMAD AL-SHRAIDEH

Full stack web developer

Address: Jordan, Amman

Email: mhmd.shrydh1996@gmail.com

Phone: 00962795956190 Portfolio: click here

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Passionate full stack web developer with very good Knowledge and excellent experience of JavaScript frameworks, Able to function effectively as an independent worker or as part of a team, gaining valuable experience while being innovative and flexible represents my ultimate goals.

Projects

AkarCom : full stack Real Estate website.

E-commerce: React Js application.

ToDo App: React Js application.

Movie App: React Js application.

Live Chat app: full stack application.

Dev university: html and css website.

EXPERIENCE

2022/4-present <u>ASAC</u> - internship as JavaScript full stack web developer.

2019/3-2021/3 AL-FAISAL Contracting CO. site engineer.

EDUCATION

2014-2019 Yarmouk university-Civil engineering/construction management.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- 1. Javascript frameworks: NodeJs, ReactJs.
- 2. Javascript libraries
 - a. backend: Express, axios, superagent, Jest, jwt,...etc.
 - b. frontend: react-redux, redux-toolkit, redux-thunk, react-router-dom, react-bootstrap, material UI, node-sass.
- 3. HTML and CSS.
- 4. PostgresSQL.
- 5. Projects deployment: Heroku, netlify, gh-pages.
- 6. Data structure and algorithms.
- 7. Git and GitHub.

SOFT SKILLS

- 1. Team work.
- 2. Time management.
- 3. Problem solving.
- 4. Fast learning.